hitsviral.com 2019-08-06

# HitsViral

Privacy Policy

 **This Privacy Policy explains how HitsViral (HitsViral, HitsViral.com, "we" or "us") uses and protects any information that you give HitsViral when you use this website.**

For information about our Terms of Service, [click here](http://hitsviral.com/terms.php).  
For information about our Disclaimers, [click here](http://hitsviral.com/disclaimers.php).  
For information about our Anti-Spam Policy, [click here](http://hitsviral.com/anti-spam_policy.php).

This Privacy Policy describes the information that we gather on or through the Service, how we use and disclose such information, and the steps we take to protect such information. By visiting the Site, or by purchasing or using the Service, you accept the privacy practices described in this Policy.

## Definitions

**"Client"** means a customer of HitsViral.

**"Client Data"** means personal data, reports, addresses, and other files, folders or documents in electronic form that a User of the Service stores within the Service.

**"Personal Data"** means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

**"Public Area"** "means the area of the Site that can be accessed both by Users and Visitors, without needing to log in.

**"Members Area"** means the area of the Site that can be accessed only by Users, and where access requires logging in.

**"User"** means an employee, agent, or representative of a Client, who primarily uses the restricted areas of the Site for the purpose of accessing the Service in such capacity.

**"Visitor"** means an individual other than a User, who uses the public area, but has no access to the restricted areas of the Site or Service.

## Collection of Personal Information

**User-provided Information**

HitsViral collects, uses and stores information including your name, Username, Password, email address and Internet Protocol (IP) address when you sign up in order to create an account for you. 

We collect the email address associated with any payments made and store the date, time and details of items purchased and payment method used. We do not store any banking or payment details as we use third party processors to process transactions.

**"Automatically Collected" Information**

HitsViral collects usage habits that include a list of dates and times the site is accessed via login and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of account logins. 

We use cookies and web beacons to provide information on how you use our web services and advertising products. These are collected and used by automated technologies to ensure we provide the best experience to suit your needs.

**Integrated / Third Party Services**

Other automated technologies that HitsViral uses include the use of third party widgets and plugins such as Facebook Like buttons and pop up ad technologies to ensure you see the advert once per session etc. That information is subject to the privacy policies of those providers.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information that we collect in a variety of ways in providing the Service and operating our business, including the following:

**Operations**

We use account information (Name, Username, Password & Internet Protocol Address) to enable use to provide a Members Area from where you can manage your own advertising and store the information about what adverts you have purchased and have available including account balances.

**Improvements**

We use the information regarding transactions (Date, Time, Email Address Used, Purchased Item Information and Payment Method Used) to process your transactions and to keep a log of what you have purchased in the past in case of any discrepancies you may have about what you have purchased. We also use this information to enable us to see what items sell well and improve on our best products and offerings.

**Communications**

We use your email address to validate and confirm that you are the account holder and so that you can click the opt in verification link to give your approval of us contacting you via email. This helps us keep you informed, send details of purchases for your records and also to verify the account holder for security reasons. We also promote other products and services (both supplied or provided by us or by third parties) to you via email but we do so from emails sent directly from our system only and do not share or distribute your email address with others. (See the "Linking to other websites" section below)

**Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Automated cookies and web beacons are used for tracking purposes to see from where Members have come and to keep session information to make sure that certain ads are only delivered once per session and not every page load.

## To Whom We Disclose Information

We do not share your email address with any third parties and never sell member information. We do allow third parties to advertise using our services and we do promote other services to you via email but all promotions are delivered from our systems and no personal information is shared with them from us. You may share information with them if you join their site or purchase their services.

**Service Providers**

We may provide information including Name, Email Address and Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses to both payment processors and or law enforcement if requested to do so by law and or the terms of purchasing using their services to help with any investigation or information request they need to conduct lawful business.

We may use your information in our other businesses but all communication will come via the account and system that you signed up for and not our other services unless you register there and give separate permission there.

Any information collected by third party apps or plugins including but not limited to Facebook Like buttons etc is picked up from your actions and not from our system by way you interact with such services and therefore you are using their service and under their privacy policies.

**Change of Ownership**

Should the website and or business be sold, the information collected will be passed over to the new business or website owner. However, it will remain intact in the confines of the site. The new owner will be as part of any sales agreement, the new owner will be required to comply and follow this Privacy Policy until notifying Users of any changes.

**Law Enforcement, Legal Process and Compliance**

We may disclose Personal Data or other information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with applicable laws, in response to (on face-value) valid court order, judicial or other government subpoena or warrant, or to otherwise cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental agencies.

We also reserve the right to disclose Personal Data or other information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to (i) take precautions against liability, (ii) protect ourselves or others from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or activity, (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, (iv) protect the security or integrity of the Service and any facilities or equipment used to make the Service available, or (v) protect our property or other legal rights, enforce our contracts, or protect the rights, property, or safety of others.

## Your Choices

**Your Options & Acceptance**

You stated that you have read and agreed to the Terms of Service for using this site when you checked/ticked the box indicating your Agreement to the Terms of Service. Part of that agreement includes the acceptance of this Privacy Policy. You are also required to double opt in to our Mail & Newsletter Service which means by clicking on the Agreement link in the email we sent to confirm your email address. Failure to verify within 7 days will result in account deletion and all information held being erased automatically.

You can Unsubscribe and/or Remove your account by yourself at any time. All emails from us excluding the Welcome email have an Unsubscribe link which will enable you to remove your account at any time. You can also do this from inside your Members Area via the Profile Page and Delete Account button. This will cancel any future use of your information and remove your account from our system.

**Your Right To View, Edit & Delete Personal Information**

If at any time you would like to view or edit account information including email address name and Passwords you can do so by logging into the inside the HitsViral Members Area on your Profile Page. You can also delete your account anytime that you wish from the delete account button on the Profile Page inside the Members Area. This removes all information we hold excluding the log of purchases made, which we hold for accounting and tax purposes only.

You may also request to see all the information we hold for you but we will require you to prove your identification before providing that information. This is done for data security and privacy reasons and if we are not sure if you are the person the information requested is for then we reserve the right to withhold that provision until such times as we can be certain by requesting more proof.

To request the information we retain on you or to get us to delete or edit your information please submit a [GDPR & Privacy Data Request Ticket by cliking here](http://help.trafficinsider.net/) (or by visiting <http://help.trafficinsider.net/>) using the same email address and name registered on your account. We will then reply to that ticket requesting further proof of your identity to ensure we only give the information to you.

You can request your Password at any time using the Password Retrieval Link on the login page. For security reasons all Passwords are encrypted and our staff have no access to them. Make sure your email address is correct and up-to-date because the only way to request it is through that link.

## Third-Party Services

We promote and link to other third party websites and services. When visiting or using one of these other services or websites you should ensure you review their privacy policies and Terms of Service. HitsViral is not responsible for the policies and practices of any third party service or site.

## Cookies & Other Tracking Information Used

Cookies (A text file that websites send to a visitor's computer or device) are used to identify the visitor's web browser or to store information or settings in the web browser. The same as most websites, we uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your online experience when using our services. We use cookies to track the total number of visitors to a website and also to remember you when you next visit the site.

We use web beacons and javascript to provide services and features on our site that you use when using our services and to better improve the services and tailor them to your needs.

Cookies also enable us to keep you logged in to the Members Area. Logging in then deleting your cookies then continuing to try and use the Members Area will log you out of your account. This is why the use of cookies is important to providing you with site and service access.

You can control and delete cookies and enable and disable javascript in your browser settings. The way you set up your browser determines if these are used and that is under your control. Please note some features and services may not work with javascript disabled.

**The Following Types of Cookies Are Used in the Site:**

  * strictly necessary/essential cookies - These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for cannot be provided. These cookies don't collect information that identifies a visitor.

  * performance cookies - These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don't collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.

  * functionality cookies - These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your User name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

  * behaviorally targeted advertising cookies - These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaigns. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator's permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, our website will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

Under our Terms of Service and Conditions of Use, children under 18 are not allowed to use our website and access our services. It is not our intention to offer products or services to minors.

## Data Security

HitsViral is committed to taking all appropriate measures in regards to the security of all information collected and stored. We have systems in place to protect against the accidental, unlawful or unauthorized loss, access & disclosure of all information. No website or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**Notification of Breaches or Other Issues**

Although we take security very seriously, should the worst happen and any data is compromised we will notify you by email within 72 hours.

**User Passwords**

Passwords are encrypted and even the staff at HitsViral do not have access to that so please use the Password retrieval tool to regain lost Passwords.

## Data Retention

We only retain the Personal Data collected from a User for as long as the User's account is active or otherwise for a limited period of time as long as we need it to fulfill the purposes for which we have initially collected it, unless otherwise required by law. We will retain and use information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our Agreements as follows:

  * the contents of closed accounts are deleted immediately when the account is closed.

  * backups are kept for 1 month.

## Notice of Compliance to California Residents

Your California Privacy Rights Under The California Online Privacy Protection Act and the California Business and Professions Code  
This privacy policy identifies thecategories of personally identifiable information that our company collects through our Web site or online service, about individual consumers who use or visit our company's commercial Web site or online service and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom our company may share that personally identifiable information.  
Our company does not maintain a process for an individual consumer who uses or visits our commercial Web site or online service to review and request changes to any of hisor her personally identifiable information that is collected through our Web site or online service.

See the section below entitled "Change Notice" for a description of the process by which our company notifies consumers who use or visit our commercial Web site or online service of material changes to our company's privacy policy for this Web site or online service.  
The effective date of this privacy policy is listed at the end of this privacy policy under the heading, "Last updated."  
For the purposes of this policy and California compliance the following definitions apply:  
Depending on the visitor's activity, in our commercial Web site or online service, the following "personally identifiable information" may be collected, in addition to information set forth in other sections of this document.  
The term "personally identifiable information" means individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected online by our company from an individual and maintainedby our company inan accessible form, and may include any of the following:

  * (1) A first and last name.

  * (2) A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town.

  * (3) An e-mail address.

  * (4) A telephone number.

  * (5) A social security number.

  * (6) Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual.

  * (7) Information concerning a user that the Web site or online service collects online, from the user, and maintains in personally identifiable form, in combinationwith an identifier described within this privacy policy.

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to Privacy@PrivacyRequest.com and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, the domain name of the Web site you are inquiring about, along with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request.

## Change Notice

HitsViral may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make a change we will change it here on this page and update the last updated date at the bottom of the page. We encourage you to return to this page from time to time to check for updates and revisions.

## Questions/Comments/Concerns or How To Reach Us

If you have any questions about the contents of this page, or simply wish to reach us for any other reason, you may do so by using the [contact us](http://trafficinsider.net/contact-us/) page on TrafficInsider.net located at <http://trafficinsider.net/contact-us/>.

You may also use the Help Desk located at <http://help.trafficinsider.net/>

**You can send physical mail to:**

4251 FM 2181 Suite #230-356,  
Corinth, TX 76210

Last updated: June 27, 2019

Please note that this Privacy Policy, as well as all other content in HitsViral, is subject to copyright.
